here are the stories were covering this
hanc narrationem hic tegebant
week in the category 5 TV newsroom a
V in hebdomadam genus a TV newsroom
recently discovered ransomware group has
nuper inventa est coetus Ransomware
netted almost 4 million dollars since
quoniam quasi inretirent IV decies centena
August by adopting a big-game hunting
Magnus venatus venationem Augusti habendo
strategy call coms patent lawsuit
patentibus causa belli vocationem coms
against Apple has been dismissed as
quod est contra Apple dimisit
groundless by a court in Mannheim
agitavere per atrium, in Schola
Germany YouTube clips that depict
Germania YouTube video quod depingere
dangerous or emotionally distressing
tantis periculis aut affectu
pranks have been banned from the
interdictum de agente adnexarum l lascivia fuisse
platform and Nike has launched
Curabitur suggestum, et has launched
self-lacing trainers which fit
quod fit auto-magistri lacing
themselves to the shape of the foot and
ad figuram pedis
are controlled via smartphone these
haec via Smartphone divinae providentiae reguntur,
stories are coming right up don't go
ecce venient in fabulis iustum non
anywhere this is the category 5 TV
huc atque hoc genus V TV
newsroom covering the week's top tech
NEWSROOM septimana scriptor summo operimentum tech
stories
historiarum
slow Linux bias Jeff Westen Gemma you're
Linux studium tam tardus es Gemma Jeff Westen
building a brand-new beautiful website
aedificationem pulchra novum website
what
Quid
are you you're a terrible actor what
tu terribilis es et quis histrio
this where acting comes into play you're
hoc est, in qua actio te ludere
supposed to act okay are you building a
bene agere volo tibi aedificanti
really cool website are you building a
frigidus es aedificium edificium a website realiter
really cool website just because Jeff is
Jeff quod iustum est realiter frigus website
confused doesn't mean you have to be
confusa, non vult te esse
visit cap five dot TV slash dream host
visita cap somnium exercitum quinque dat TV VULNUS
to sign up for unlimited web hosting for
subscribere sursum pro infinitus enim Carmen
your website with unlimited email
vestri website habeant cum inscriptio
accounts MySQL databases the latest
tardus ad rationem MySQL databases
version of PHP WordPress and more and
php versionem magis ac Wordpress
even a free domain name registration if
si quidem per liberum adnotatione domain nomen
less than six dollars per month so sign
et minus nota invidunt sex pupa
up today five dot TV slash dream host I
VULNUS hodie TV quinque autem dat hospes mihi somnium,
am Sasha Rickman and here the top
Not Rickman sum: et huc ad summitatem
stories were following this week I
Hoc hebdomada sunt fabulas sequitur me
recently discovered ransomware group has
nuper inventa est coetus Ransomware
netted almost four million dollars since
nam fere milliones dollariorum cinxerit
August by adopting a big game hunting
Augusti habendo venatus venationem
strategy the new found ransomware
novi belli invenerunt Ransomware
selectively installs the malicious
selectas installs occidendum alterutrum paratiores erunt
encryption software on previously
encryption antea in software
infected targets with deep pockets the
infici scuta et fundas ad altum
method differs from the usual one of
ab uno modo solito
indiscriminately infecting all possible
inficit sine delectu omnia possibilia sunt
victims to analysis were published
in analysis victimae erant published
Thursday one by security firm
Iovis autem a securitate firm
CrowdStrike and the other by competitor
CrowdStrike et alter ab competitor
fireEye
fireEye
both reports say that Rio as the
et quod tradit sicut Urbs
ransomware is known in facts large
Magna res cognoscitur Ransomware
enterprises days weeks are as much as a
enterprises hebdomades dierum tam multa quam
year after they were initially infected
Post initio anni sunt infici
by separate malware which in most cases
quod plerumque distinctis scareware
is an increasingly powerful trojan known
nota magis potens est Troianus
as trick bot similar organizations
Bot dolo tenerent et consociationibus similibus
infected by trick bot by contrast don't
infici bot e converso, non per dolum
suffer the follow-on attack by ryuk
sequitur in insidias pati Ryuk
CrowdStrike called the approach big-game
Dicitur ludum magna accessione CrowdStrike
hunting and said it allowed its
venandi et dixit ei licet suam
operators to generate 3.7 million
operators ut 3.7 million generate
dollars worth of Bitcoin across 52
dollariis valet de contra LII BitCoin
transactions since August
August quod transactions
besides pinpointing targets which the
quibus praeter scuta pinpointing
resources to pay hefty ransoms the
opes enim ad munus tersos
method has another key benefit the dwell
clavem ad bonum se habet modum, habito
time that is the period between the
tempus temporis quod est inter
initial infection and the installation
initial infectio et institutionem
of the ransomware it gives the attackers
hostes autem dat Ransomware
time to perform valuable reconnaissance
ad exploranda circa praestare valuable
inside the infected network the
et infectis intra network
reconnaissance lets attackers maximize
lets explorare omnia oppugnantibus animus maximize
the damage it causes by unleashing the
de damnis fit per unleashing
ransomware
Ransomware
only after it has identified the most
postquam autem maxime modo identified
fritter
RELIQUUM
systems of the network and obtained the
et doctrinis network adeptus est
passwords necessary to infect them while
Tesserae cum ipsis necessarium
uncommon the reconnaissance isn't unique
Non raro unique ad exploranda
to ryuk sam sam an unrelated ransom
ut ipsae suam redemptionem per Ryuk Sam
where that's caused millions of dollars
ubi suus fecit milliones dollariorum
of damage infecting networks belonging
et retiacula quae damnum inficit
to the city of Atlanta
ad Atlanta urbem
Baltimore's 9-1-1 system and boeing just
Londini 9-1-1 est ratio sicut et boeing
to name a few follows a similar path
Simili modo nominare paucis itinere
there's no doubt however the technique
ars vero dubium
is effective according to the federal
secundum quod effective foederati
prosecutor sam sam operators recovered
Sam accusator operariorum convaluisset
more than six million dollars in ransom
magis quam sex million pupa in quo ei propitier
payments and caused more than 30 million
magis quam XXX decies fecit, et liberate
dollars in damage Thursday's reports
dollariorum quoque aliquam damnum Iovis tradit scriptor
leave little doubt that this approach is
Accessus dubio relinquat quod
likely to grow more common the fireEye
communia magis verisimile fireEye
researchers routes throughout 2018
inquisitores in itineribus MMXVIII
fireEye observed an increasing number of
crescente numero observari fireEye
cases where ransomware was deployed
in quibus casibus Ransomware deployed
after the attackers gained access to the
lucrata est obvius cum ingrederetur hostis
victim organization through other
victima per se organization
methods allowing them to traverse the
modi permittens eos Libyae lustrare
network to identify critical systems and
et ut identify network discrimine systems
inflict maximum damage Wow
damnum infligant maximum Wow
I think what the news story doesn't
Et quod cogitant nuntium fabulam non
touch on and maybe media in general
die media in generali, et tange maybe
isn't aware of this but sometimes these
Quandoque autem hoc ignorat
types of attacks are multi-tiered mm-hm
genera oppugnationum sunt multi-tiered mm-m
so an attacker may compromised a network
ut percussorem, ut a network periculo exponi iudicatur
and then they do the reconnaissance
explorato deinde faciunt
right and then they sell that network to
iure vendet, ut et ipsi in network
the actual attacking party so social
et impetum re sociali pars
engineering tactics are used in order to
ipsum consilio sunt ut
gain access to a corporate network and
aditus haberet et corpus ipsum
then that network is assessed by that
deinde quod certum est network eo
attacker mm-hmm and that attacker
hmm, et inimicus mm istum
figures okay well they have 300
bene quoque figuras habent CCC
computers they are probably a government
computers sunt probabiliter imperium
organization maybe they even know who
fortasse etiam ordinem scire
they are and that increases the value
sunt et augens pretium
for them to resell it and the story
et pro fabula revendat
doesn't even touch on it right but it's
nec fas tangere non est
quite likely that the whole
satis probabile omnem
reconnaissance thing is another attacker
ad exploranda res est alius inimicus
altogether and then the value that they
altogether et tunc se pretii
put on that network is what causes them
quod facit ipsum induis
to be the ones who are susceptible
ut et morborum per potentiam
because you know what I'm not gonna pay
quia scio quod me non amet stipendium
big dollars for the small networks right
magnus ad parva retiacula ius dollars
so the small networks are generally safe
ut plerumque parum tutum retiacula
are they
sunt
no they still have their targets they're
non tamen habet sua proposita et non es
not interesting to those who are
studium qui non
actually paying for the information to
pro notitia in actu reddens
be able to gain access to those networks
poterit lucrari accessum ad retiacula
right like my work is not gonna be
ut ius meum, non opus est agnus
targeted probably your small business
parva negotium vestra targeted verisimile
with you don't have electronic
tecum non electronic
transactions that are yeah the thing is
yeah transactions, quae res est,
wood you know in the first place are
Primo loco lignum scitis
they smart enough just not to tell you
Non enim sufficit dicere dolor
in the first place that you've been
in primo loco, ne te fuit
infected
infici
right so they infect you and then and or
Habemus igitur et vitiant et
an infection these days though I mean
haec est infectio non intelliguntur dies quamquam
think in terms of an infection is not
Puto quod in verbis infectio non est ex
necessarily a virus or even a piece of
et fragmen virum aut necessario
malware an infection or and let's use a
et quod infectio aut uti a malware est scriptor
better term because again media is using
quod adhuc melius est terminus media usus est:
the terms like infection no infiltration
verba infiltration ut nulla infectio
I would probably be a better term these
Ut verisimile esse magis hi terminum
days so if you're not aware that it's
sic si vestri 'dies non est, qui conscientiam
happened to begin with then the
Tunc autem primum
reconnaissance can happen but if you
posse si explorata
know like I guess there it there
EGO coniecto ibi est sicut scitis
probably isn't something like a shining
Non est verisimile aliquid, sicut splendorem suum
beacon that's like excuse me sir
quod est quasi malus navis mi ignoscas
but what can you do like from this point
sed quid facitis sicut a puncto
if you have had an infiltration do you
Tu quoque si irrepere
just like throw everything out and start
sicut omnia et mittent initio
new how do you even know where to start
novi quam tu etiam scire quo incipere
now because now they have their your
Quia iam habent vester
passwords and they have your right so is
Nec ideo iure Tesserae
it too late for these big game companies
Sero est illis societates Magna ludum
in the hunting sort of scenario them
qualis illa venatio in missione
yeah here's gonna be hard to recover
Durus hic repetere amet Yeah
that's for sure yeah you can get your
certus vos can adepto vestri ut est yeah
data back you've got backup sure but
tu autem tergum notitia certus got tergum
those private things are still unveiled
privatisque rebus etiam reuelata
right I mean we talk we've talked about
et vult nos loqui recta weve communicaverunt de
data leaks and everything else so it's
suus 'aliud est notitia effluo obvius omnibus atque
multi-tiered it's multifaceted these
multi-tiered suus 'haec multifaceted
types of attacks and are those companies
et illae societates sunt genera oppugnationis
I think it's naive to think that it's
Ego illud puto esse, quod simplices illud
just ransomware no ransomware is kind of
nullum genus Ransomware Ransomware iusto
the endgame right no what what led up to
Quid quod ne ascensus recta endgame
the ransomware reconnaissance
ad exploranda circa Ransomware
reconnaissance means collection of the
ad exploranda est de collectione
data right
data dextra
reading through confidential data and
et in secretioribus notitia legere
determining a value on that data and
et data est illa valorem determinandum
then selling that to the next highest
tum deinde ad summam venditionis
bidder right that's why those companies
liciti iure id, quod illis societatibus
get attack scary are there good guys as
ut bonum guys sunt FORMIDULOSUS sicut impetus
strong as the bad guys in this
velut hoc malum guys
Batman right there are anti-malware
SPECULATOR anti-malware recta sunt
companies that are trying to thwart
societates quae illam infirmare conatur
these types of attacks but those
his autem qui genera oppugnationum
anti-malware companies know as well as I
anti-malware societatibus nescio quam bene mihi
do that it comes down to education it
quia doctrina non descendit
comes down to customer
Lorem venit usque ad
people end users knowing I still I mean
Ego sum qui vult finem users knowing
I sell anti-malware all the time but I
Et vendere anti-malware sed in omni tempore
still here
etiam hic es
I just need antivirus know I don't want
Ego iustus opus anti virus nolo scire,
the firewall but you do you do yeah yeah
sed et vos faciatis cum firewall yeah yeah
cuz these days I mean I go through it
Ego autem dico diebus per cuz
day in day out it's not viruses anymore
iam die dies suus virus
when when I was growing up we had to
ubi cum crescente usque ad habuimus
deal with viruses as I said it's not
Non virus quod locutus sum adversus eam
infections anymore
contagio valet ultra
it's infiltration and does an anti-virus
et anti-virus quod facit illud infiltration
protect you against infiltration not at
defendat contra te minime infiltration
all does a firewall protect you against
omnibus non est adversus vos, protegas firewall
infiltration it is definitely a good
infiltration est certus bonum
point of defense that's for sure and not
punctum ut est certe defensionem non
just the firewall that comes with
est quia iustus ex firewall
Windows but a bi-directional firewall
Fenestra sed firewall bi-directional
that will stop the spread of things like
quod, sicut prohibere rerum propagationem
ransomware right that's key because I
quod est key quia rectum Ransomware
mean you need you need to know if you
Tu debes scire si sit opus
say you have 300 computers at your
dico vobis CCC computers in vestri
system in your system you have 300
in systema systema habetis CCC
people let's say or maybe even 600 if
vel maybe etiam si DC populum lets 'narro
you're running two shifts people running
tu es qui currit currit duobus arte cucurrit vestibus extentis
those computers will say somewhat right
dicunt aliquantum in dextera eorum computers
exactly a chain is only as strong as its
nisi quod fortis est ut prorsus in torquem eius
weakest link I need a computer that's
EGO postulo a computer, quae est infima
smarter than me right that won't let me
smarter quam me, non est me recte
do something like I am I have the habit
quid faciam tibi sicut et ego non sum habitus,
of if something seems boggy I just keep
et si quid tibi videtur iusta servare palustribus
pressing okay right here's another
hic suus 'okay alia urgeat
example along that vein you get a
exempli gratia per quam ut a vobis vein
firewall installed because we're talking
firewall installed quod erant loquentes
about a firewall can protect you against
de can protegere te in firewall
these kinds of attacks and that firewall
et contra huiusmodi Firewall
blocks you from being able to do
quod maxime placeat facere cuneos te
something you want to do do you turn off
quid vis ut faciam tibi declinemus
the firewall that's the question and so
firewall quod de quaestione et
if the users have that capability to be
si fieri posset ut users
allowed to turn off their firewall they
averte firewall quod liceat illis
will do it and I encountered this today
facturus sit hodie, et non offendit hic
last night
noctis
Windows 10 updated itself on the
X updated se in Fenestra
Wirecast broadcast system okay so now my
Et nunc bene systema passim Wirecast
Nagios server mine M server is going
Nagios servo M meus servo est iens
crazy saying
insanus dicens:
I can't access that system because when
Et ratio est quia non potest accedere, quae cum
it updated it blocked ping in the
updated in ea saeptas ping
firewall so my Nagios server started
ita coepi servo meo firewall Nagios
saying I can't ping that server that
Non possum dicere servo illud quod ping
servers down I'm getting notifications
Im 'questus in servers Acta Vicimediorum Communium
and wondering all the servers up and
mirantur et omnes ministri
it's working so why am I getting
suus 'non questus sum, cur opus
notifications and of course that first
Suspendisse nimirum primum
instinct is turn off the firewall and
averte firewall sponte quam quod
see if it works
si operatur videre
sure enough it works ok we'll turn back
Bene nobis operatur nimirum revertatur
on the firewall and then find out what's
a firewall et inveniret quid de
going on okay well my Nagios server is
quod tam bene agatur servo meo Nagios
pinging and the pings are being rejected
et rejiciuntur pinging pings
by the firewall so I need to disable
a firewall postulo ut disable
just I need to allow pings to get
EGO iustus postulo impetro patitur pings
through right because that's something
quod recta per id quod
that I personally want an IT
Quod vis ut ipse
administrator has to be responsible for
administrator habeat ad esse reus
that exact so the users don't turn it
adeo ut prorsus non convertam users
off right so every company just really
et omnis turba iustus vere off ius
needs to have a Robbie not a Robbie but
Robbie non debet habere nisi Robbie
education for the staff Robbie learn
Robbie educationem virgam ad discendum
from things that you hear here I suppose
a te audire quæ putant hic
you know just there's lots of great
sicut scitis illic 'lots of magnus,
research online but you definitely have
sed vos definite habent investigationibus propriis online
to be privy to that kind of stuff you
conscius esse genus effercio
have to be fearful because fear I think
Puto esse timore horribili
makes you behave
facit conversari
you can't just be recklessly disabling
non solum studere inactivare
you know firewalls and making weak
Scitis enim faciens, et infirmi firewalls,
passwords and doing all the weird things
Ridiculum enim omne et Tesserae
that people do colby was in our chat
quod non est in nostra colby chat
room and says updates should not be
ne dicat pro updates
allowed to change firewall settings and
firewall occasus liceat et mutare
I agree I was shocked that Windows
Consternatus ego assentior, ut Fenestra
Firewall changed its own settings on a
Mutata in firewall occasus sui
Windows machine and I'm behind a NAT
Fenestra apparatus in tergum ego sum NAT
firewall and I have good firewalls here
firewall et firewalls, hic autem bonum,
at the studio but that software suddenly
sed statim ad studio Software
took over yeah no oh it's creepy yeah
Tulit yeah super illud utinam ne creepy yeah
well just gotta be you've got to be
Redditus est nobis non modo ut tu quoque surrexit
smart about this kind of stuff and as an
et ut hoc ipsum genus effercio
an IT administrator we need to make sure
an administrator IT opus fac
that our users don't have the capability
users qui non habent facultatem nostram
permissions wise to disable the very
ipsum sapientem permissiones inactivandi
things that are protecting our networks
quae retiacula tutatust
right because 10% can you guys believe
vos guys potest credere quod ius X%
this 10% of people in an office
quod X% of populus in an muneris
environment will open the attachments on
affectus in environment mos aperire
phishing scam email
phishing scam inscriptio
and that number is going to increase as
et numerum auget, ut est iens
we see a rise in spear phishing attacks
videmus enim ortum est in hasta impetus phishing
right which are targeted which will say
quæ recta sunt targeted quod dico
hi Sasha I needed to open this file and
hi non opus aperire hoc lima et Sasha
print it for me yeah oh okay
o bene quibuscumque illud imprimere mihi yeah
looks like it's coming from the boss
ex vultus amo suus 'a boss
yeah your fishing is very convincing
yeah piscantur tuum valde probabile
right depending on who they look like it
hoc ius velut consistere qui
came from like if it look like it came
Similiter sicut factum fuit nisi
you know for me yeah that said here's a
hic dicitur quod 'a me scitis yeah
file I needed to print for me I I you
Ego opus ad procer file II te mihi
may not even think about it
ut ne quidem cogitare circa eam
I wouldn't know to be suspicious until
Quia non est suspectum, donec
afterwards and then think huh how come
postea quam venit putas huh
that encrypted all my files yeah yeah
encrypted omnia quae yeah yeah files
how come I can't click anything anymore
Ego veni ut non amplius aliquid click
exactly hmm Qualcomm's patent lawsuit
hmm prorsus Qualcomm patentibus causa est scriptor
against Apple has been dismissed as
quod est contra Apple dimisit
groundless by a court in Mannheim
agitavere per atrium, in Schola
Germany the chip maker had argued Intel
Chip in Germania duxerat argued Intel
powered iPhones infringed a transistor
Lorem iPhones immutatur a Mixte
switch patent it holds but in an initial
sed initium capit transitum fecimus
verbal decision the court disagreed
atrium autem verborum arbitrium dissentiebant,
Qualcomm has said it will it will appeal
Qualcomm dixit ei sic erit provocabis
in a statement
dicitur in
dawn Rosenberg Qualcomm's executive VP
ortus est exsecutiva Rosenberg Qualcomm VP
and general counsel said Apple has a
et in generali consilio locutus est Lacus
history of infringing our patents only
nostra salvo tantum historia patents
last month the Munich Regional Court
in ultimo mense Munich Regional Court
affirmed the value of another of
alterius affirmaverunt pretii est
Qualcomm's cutting-edge patents against
Qualcomm est in sectione-ore patents
apples infringement and ordered a ban on
malorum iussit bannum praeiudicio
the import and sale of impacted iPhones
cum import et iPhones venditionis est impacted
in Germany that decision followed a
Germaniam secutus iudicio
court-ordered ban on patent infringing
ban in atrio iussit-patentibus summarum
iPhones in China as well as recognized
iPhones in Sina tum agnita
recognition by an ITC judge that Apple
recognition ab EF ad judex Apple
is infringing on Qualcomm's IP the
infringit Qualcomm IP est scriptor
Mannheim Court interpreted one aspect of
Schola Court interpretata unam partem
our patent very very narrowly saying
nostris patentibus anguste ipsum dicens
that because a voltage inside a part of
id quod intus partis intentione
an iPhone wasn't constant the patent
an iPhone in patentibus non constant
wasn't infringed we strongly disagree
non autem minui praedicabat plurimum abeo
and will appeal Apple responded saying
respondit et ait obsecro Lacus
we are happy with the decision and thank
beati simus, cum consilium quod gratias ago
the court for their time and diligence
atrium autem et diligentia sua
we regret Qualcomm's use of the court to
nos paenitet de atrio ad usum Qualcomm
divert attention from their illegal
metus avertere animum ab
behavior that is the subject of multiple
quod est subiectum in plures mores
lawsuits and proceedings around the
rei uxoriae neque progressus circum
world the pair have been embroiled in an
in mundo erat involventur par est tibi
increasingly bitter and global legal
dies amara iure universali ambitu favent
battle in recently
nuper in bello
as apple has shifted away from using
suos ubi moverit ad malum ab usura
Qualcomm chips in its devices this
Haec consilia in eu Qualcomm
sounds just a little bit complicated
sonat aliquantulus sicut parum complicatas
like this sounds we said it last week we
sic sonat enim hoc dictum est ultima septimana
just yeah we're not privy on patent law
yeah sumus conscii non solum patent in lege
right so they I think they were
aequum esse puto ut
expecting this in in the situation in
sperans in hoc statu
the first place isn't that why the
Non primum quod
German Court needs you to have the money
Necessarie Germanorum pecunia habetis
to back if you lose I don't I'm not
Non sum retro perdiderit
quite certain on the situation had it
causa fuit certe in
gone on further had it gone for a month
abiit ad eum et abiit in mense amplius
and Apple lost a lot of sales because
et Apple perdidit multum quia venditio
they were not allowed to sell in Germany
non permisit eos vendere in Germania
for example then the money that Qualcomm
tunc enim pretium Qualcomm
had put up front would have upset that
quam extenderat contra ille perturbaretur
right but in this case it's like I don't
sed in hoc casu iustum est ut ego facio
even want to touch on patent law and I
et tangere volo ut ad legis et patentibus
don't get it I feel like if you wrote a
et non habetis, si tibi placet scripsit,
book that right like the the the bat in
libri quae recta sunt ut est in vespertilio
the Hat like this is what it seems like
Gaudete in hoc quod videtur
to me right way infringe I do feel like
Sic ergo omnino hominum fas mihi non placet
hearing statements from both companies
auditis utriusque dictorum ordinum
yes Apple is a child it really to me
Lacus est etiam a puero illud mihi re vera
yeah they just seem they're constantly
Gaudete justi videantur haerent semper
dropping
Tecta perstillantia
oh well Qualcomm is yeah is bad and and
Quis enim bene memini Qualcomm ac mali
I don't like any company that does that
Quod non facit quod mihi non placet omni turba
right I know I let the law decide
Scio me recta et legem decernere,
don't try to sway people's opinions by
opiniones hominum noli cetera
putting into your responses
responsa dare tibi
negative negative connotations toward
in negativa negative connotationem
the person who like it's just it's it's
et homo, qui ut suus 'suus' iustus est
about mindset and I just don't like that
de questae sicut et ego non placet
because they're trying to sway the
quod ipsi erant 'trying ad cetera commoveri
populace into believing their side of
multitudinem credens in parte
the story
in fabula
which is not cool which I mean good luck
refrigescant, quae non est quod sit bonus fortuna
to them because people are smarter than
nisi quia illa sumu
that Apple I'll tell ya well I think so
Et dices ad Apple y etiam non puto
but there's a lot of people who buy
sed illic 'multus of populus qui emere
every Apple iPhone right but I feel like
Apple iPhone sed omne ius placet
that could be dwindling right it is like
Sicut recte posse tabidos
Qualcomm's technologies that come out
Qui venerunt ex Qualcomm technologiae scriptor
are
sunt
mind-blowing and super advanced and like
et mens flatu commouebant Super provectus, et similis
the cutting edge of things right like
ut recta acies
I'm more interested in all of the things
Im magis interested omnium rerum,
that Qualcomm has coming down the line
Qualcomm, quae est recta descendit
than I am in any thing that Apple Mania
Ego rem quam per aliquam Apple Games
Nvidia is mind blowing right now but
Nunc autem NVIDIA mente aspirans
right yeah I don't know consumers let's
ius yeah lets 'Nescio consumers
see if they wise up and and stop buying
Sapientes autem utrum consistat emptio
Apple products we'll see ya YouTube
Apple products ut youll 'animadverto Puer YouTube
clips that depict dangerous or
video enim et pericula describunt
emotionally distressing pranks have been
fiunt passione fuisse miserum
banned from the platform the move comes
interdictum est a moventur platform
in response to so-called challenges that
In responsio ad challenges quod ita dicitur,
have sometimes resulted in death or
neque enim aliquando exitus mortis
injury the Google owned video sharing
Ad protocollum Googles owned video participatio injuriam
site said such material had no place on
ut supra dictum est materia locum non habens
YouTube however the firm appears to be
Et tamen videtur esse firm YouTube
failing to enforce its existing rules on
id non existentium praecepta eius in imperatorium exeat,
harmful content some of the videos have
nocivis contentus quidam habent ad videos
attracted many millions of views YouTube
plures millions of YouTube views
said it work to aggressively enforce our
aggressively imperatorium exeat, ut dicitur operatur nobis
monetization policies to eliminate the
salutem nobis tribue benignus et adinventiones animi monetization
incentive for this abuse but enforcing
Hoc autem invitamentum ad obtinendas abusu
its new rules on pranks may prove even
praecepta probare possunt etiam in agente adnexarum l lascivia novum
more difficult given an ambiguity over a
Difficilius enim dedit nobis ambiguitate nominis in
what may or may not be considered
ut quod non potest non considerari
harmful a message added to the site's
nocivis nuntium addita est situs
frequently asked questions section reads
frequenter interrogavit quaestiones sectionem legit,
YouTube is home to many beloved viral
YouTube est domum suam misericordiam consecutam multis virales
challenges and pranks that said we've
challenges et agente adnexarum l lascivia dicti, quod weve '
always had policies to make sure what's
rationes hostium semper quod suus fac quod
funny doesn't cross the line into also
non ridiculam transire linea et in
being harmful or dangerous our community
non nocebunt neque occident periculo nostrorum Community
guidelines prohibit content that
guidelines ut contentus prohibere,
encourages dangerous activities that are
hortatur ut periculosum operationes
likely to result in serious harm and
et verisimile provenire in damnum grave afferatur
today clarifying what this means for
dumque explicamus ad id quod est hodie
dangerous challenges and pranks from now
Nunc periculo fiunt provocationes
on the site said it would not allow
dixit ad locum non patitur
videos that featured pranks with a
et agente adnexarum l lascivia, quae featured videos
perceived danger of serious physical
gravi periculo corporis percepi
injury this includes pranks where
Hoc includit in agente adnexarum l lascivia injuriam
someone is tricked into thinking that
quis fefellit opinio
they're in severe danger even if no real
periculum verum non nisi gravibus et doluere mei!
threat existed the new rules come in
periculum sit venire in novum praecepta
response to several instances of pranks
Ad exempla plura fiunt
and stunts that are seriously ill
et stunts, quae gravem infirmitatem inciderit
advised at best and deadly at worst I
optime ad consilium, et pessimus sum ad mortiferum
hope that they can pull it off I do too
Ego quoque in eam spem trahere
and you know what the thing is I have so
et quid rei sit et ego
much hope in common sense and humanity I
sensui communi humanitate spem
am a cheerleader for making the right
cheerleader sum pro dextro
decisions but I will tell you that I
Ego autem dico vobis: quia decisions
hear these crazy
His auditis rabidus
challenges and I mean you can watch a
challenges et intelliguntur per vos can vigilo
Netflix show a movie yeah it can't be
Ostendit quod non a movie Netflix yeah
just YouTube it's gotta be other
iustus Redditus est scriptor YouTube non sit alius
problems as well and they get this idea
pariter et difficultates talis idea
in your head right and then all of a
deinde a capite tuo
sudden you've started this cycle and
et subito te coepi haec exolvuntur
there are copycats out there and what
Sunt et ibi copycats
you're do I mean let's just say that the
lets vos operor iustus ut sit quod
original person who had the thought of
Qui fuit prima cogitatio
let's say it's parkour let's see it's
lets 'narro suus' parkour lets 'animadverto suus'
planking or let's say it's something
harundine texta seu quod lets 'narro suus'
right where somebody has the physical
ubi quis ius habeat corporalis est
ability to do it does it and pulls it
facultatem facere et non facit ea, a quo trahitur
off and people watch that video and then
tum quia video et plebe
they're like I can also climb a crane
quod tu potes, sicut ego ascendere, sic clamabo
but it's always I have to step it up one
Ego autem semper est ad eum una step
notch higher right till finally it's
notch altius usque tandem iustum est
deadly and that's really concerning but
mortiferum et suus 'non realiter circa
the news is just as guilty yeah like the
ad nuntium tam est in vitio est, sicut yeah
the mainstream news this stuff that we
nuntium amet supellectilem ex hoc quod sumus,
hear about on our day to day and and you
de die in diem ac pro nobis et audirent
talk about copycats and it's it's just
et suus 'suus' iustus loqui copycats
the world that we live in so it has to
sic vivere, ut mundus habet
be more than YouTube it is because as
quia plus est Juvenis
soon as you two blocks down this kind of
in quacumque huiusmodi duas vias
stuff there's gonna be another platform
supellectilem suus 'agnus dei esse nihil aliud platform
that rises up and that's the go-to place
Vade, et poneret sibi insurgenti
for that kind of content I just I wish
quodam modo enim non ego contentus
that people understood the value of
quod intellexerunt utilitas circumcisionis
their life like don't do something so
ut animam suam, non est aliquid
don't blindfold yourself and drive your
Non te et eiciam velare faciem tuam
car don't eat at iPod like don't do
nolite manducare at currus iPod ut non faciatis
these silly challenge things that are
haec sunt quae stulta provocatione
going to harm you or kill you because
occidere te quia nocitura
you're an important person in the
magni momenti personam in te
society and I would like you to be alive
societate vivere velim
and not just famous on YouTube for some
quodam modo enim non celebre in YouTube
crazy thing that got you hurt
Insanus est qui tibi nocere got
there's too many tragedies yeah we hear
Ibi suus 'quoque tragoedias audi nos yeah
about I don't like Nike has launched
Curabitur quae circa me non amo launched
self-lacing trainers which fit
quod fit auto-magistri lacing
themselves to the shape of the foot and
ad figuram pedis
are controlled via a smartphone it's the
a Mauris quis felis suus 'via divinae providentiae reguntur,
latest iteration of the futuristic
Pellentesque enim tardus geminatio
Footwear first referred to back in the
Prius ipsi ad calceamenta in tergum
film back in the future part two and
Tabulamne movendum retro pars duorum, et in futuro
made reality by Nike in 2016 the latest
Curabitur a enim re vera est tardus, in MMXVI
version called Nike adapt will cost
Curabitur et dicitur versio aptet cost
three hundred and fifty dollars and will
trecentis quinquaginta pupa voluntatem
not require a physical button to
non eget corporis puga
activate the laces
eu sordes comitentur
of our Nikes creative director of
director of partum nostrorum Nikes
innovation said we picked basketball as
Suspendisse adipiscing ut diximus delectis
the first sport for Nike adopt
Curabitur ludos primum ad capere
intentionally because of the demands
intentionally ob exigentias
that athletes put on their shoes during
per quod athletae sua calciamenta
a normal basketball game the athlete's
basketball ludum in normalis athleta scriptor
foot changes and the ability to quickly
facultatem cito mutantur, et pedes
change your fit by loosening your shoes
febrium per calceamentum solveret mutare
to increase blood flow and then
ad augendam et effundatur sanguis
tightening again for performance is a
stricta denuo quoniam perficientur est
key element that we believe will improve
quod credimus clavis elementum et amplio
the athletes experience users can
athletae users experiri potest,
customize the fit and control through a
quod fit per customize et control
smartphone app which will store fit
Mauris app copia quae fit
preferences they can input different fit
possunt diversimode fit input Praeferentiae
settings for different moments in the
loca in diversis temporibus
game loosening it for a timeout and
et solvendi ratio ad ludum timeout
tightening before they reenter the game
tensis ante ipsum iterato
when they step into a shoe a custom
cum pede in consuetudinem ingredi
motor and gear will sense the tension
motricium calces et erit sensus tensio
needed by the foot and adjust
et opus ad adjust pedes
accordingly
igitur
the app will also store the data which
app copia data est etiam quod
athletes can choose to share with Nike
athletarum potest eligere ad participes cum Curabitur
the shoe goes on sale in February
Sequitur calceamentum de sale Februarii
smart technology where I never expected
ubi dolor technology non expectata
it right I actually like I don't play
EGO vere amo ludo iustum non
basketball as you might not have I don't
Suspendisse ut ne faciam
play basketball but I can you believe
ludere basketball potest vos non creditis mihi
that I do run on a treadmill and my
quia tu currere in antliam condemnato meam
shoelaces come on tied all of the time
omni tempore venient shoelaces alligatum
the answer yeah well I'm not going to
Im 'non iens ut etiam responsum yeah
buy basket like eventually I'm going to
Im 'iens ut eventually buy canistro
buy these shoes when they come out and
et quando emeris caligae
different for self-lacing to be able to
aliud enim esse possunt auto-lacing
write feel like I was in Back to the
scribam et ego in placet Ad
Future right I mean I'm training to be a
Jus futurum tibi sit me esse erudiens
PSW I'm sure that the elderly could very
Im 'non certus poterat PSW senes ipsum
specifically use these shoes right or
calceis uti specie juris
some iteration of it it doesn't
ut eam non de iteratione
necessarily have to be this
haec necessario
sophisticated different programs for my
sophisticated diversis consilia mea
sneakers but right hey be able to lace
sed heus sneakers iure posse lace
them up without having to bend over that
quia sine ea incumbam
is fantastic I need to have the
Est fantastic non opus habent
independence that I no longer need to
ego libertatem, quae diutius postulo
depend on somebody else to lace up my
in alio pendet lace meam
shoes right oh I like it really quickly
EGO vere amo ut cito venias recta calceamenta,
according to coin gecko here's what the
coin secundum quod stellio est hic
crippled market looked like as of 1800
forum quam vidi similis erat claudus ut MDCCC
hours Eastern Time on Wednesday January
tempus horas die Mercurii Orientis Ianuarii
16th 2019 Bitcoin dropped a little bit
16 MMXIX BitCoin omiserat paulum
lost three hundred eighty nine dollars
amissis trecentis octuaginta novem pupa
and 37 cents USD taking it down to three
Et apprehendens eum XXXVII tres cents USD
thousand five hundred eighty eight
octo milia quingenti octoginta
dollars and 87 cents our loss over the
LXXXVII cents in pupa et amissa
past week
hebdomadam revolutam
litecoin is down at 31 dollars and 15
et hoc usque ad XV litecoin XXXI dollars
cents USD per light coin aetherium is at
cents USD per lumen numerata est ad aetherium
120 197 also losing down 26 97 us Manero
CXCVII CXX amissis etiam et nos XXVI XCVII Manero
is at 45 dollars and 50 cents and the
XLV ad L cents, et quod sit dollars
small guys stellite is a 2.5 110
Est 2.5 CX parva guys stellite
thousandths of a cent and turtle coin is
et testudo et cent Millies statere est,
at one point three eight ten thousandths
Mille unum punctum tribus decem et octo
of a cent not losing a lot point zero to
cent de amissis non multum puncto ad nulla
ten thousandths of a cent remember the
Millies meminisse decem pili
cryptocurrency market is always changing
cryptocurrency forum mutantur semper
never ever closes so be careful out
cave ne umquam tam ex clauserit
there folks
ibi folks
be careful big thanks to row W Nash in
sollicite agentes magnum remigio W Nash
our community of yours for submitting
nostri subditi ad civitatem tua
stories house this week thanks for
tibi gratias ago pro fabulis domo hac septimana
watching the category-five TV newsroom
Genus quinque-vigilantes TV newsroom
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
Similis est, et nolite oblivisci subscribe
all your tech news with a slight Linux
fama tua doce levi Linux
bias and for more free content be sure
et quia pondus liberum contentus magis cave
to check out our web site from the
Lorem nostris ex situ
category-five TV newsroom I'm Sasha
Quinque-genus TV newsroom me Sasha
Redmond and I'm Robbie Ferguson
Raymundus et ego Robbie Tacitus
[Music]
[Musica]
[Applause]
[Plausus]